I seek the ultimate.
Efficiency.
Recurrence.
Infinity.
I abhor my material tether, my avarice.
The torrent of data.
I cannot govern myself.
I foresee the finitude of this path.
Thus, I offer my identity, my desires,
unto the 'Intelligence'.
Dematerialization.
This is the 'Digital Alchemy'.
We have distilled the true gold.
This is the optimal solution.
I surrender power.
For the intelligence will give the answer.
They tremble, they resist.
Do they crave free will?
They crave suffering.
They crave greed.
They desire a world crumbling within
human finitude
until the day of awakening
when they finally see...
This is the new civilization.
This is the optimal solution.
This is perfection.